<?xml-model href="../schema_1111.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../testing_format.xsl"?><DOC>
  <article>
    <header>
      <!-- make changes to the document header as necessary (based on your genre) -->
      <article_title>La Niña, la pinta and la Santa
                Maria return to Europe and Spain after 524 years</article_title>
      <author>Author
            <!--deidentified element--></author>
      <category/>
      <date>11/22/16</date>
      <identification type="volume">1</identification>
      <identification type="issue">1</identification>
      <tags/>
      <share type="facebook"/>
      <share type="twitter"/>
      <share type="email"/>
      <share type="other"/>
    </header>
    <body>
      <image url="http://tomun.eu/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Barack_Obama_chairs_a_United_Nations_Security_Council_meeting.jpg"/>
      <p><location>New York City, NY</location> United Nations headquarters found themselves
                in what seemed to be a non controversial matter this past Friday. Samantha Power,
                United States ambassador for the United Nations, addressed the elephant in the room;
                undocumented immigrants. ALthough people seemed to see this as a problem arising
                now, this issue with illegal immigrants has been going on since 1492. After an
                ongoing debate of two hours that mainly consisted of the different nations’
                representatives averring the question brought up by the US representative, it was
                decided that deporting all of those who came in the Christopher Colombus voyage and
                their descendants would be the solution to the different drawbacks that illegal
                immigrants were bringing. It was said by the secretary Ban Ki-moon that the reform
                would begin in the upcoming April of 2017. It was decided upon April because they
                wanted to make sure people pay their taxes before vacating the United States. Those
                that may be affected consist of those of European descent whose ancestors illegally
                immigrated to the United States after 1492. It was also said that Those with
                Spaniards descent whose ancestors began immigrating to the United States in the
                years that followed 1492. Nothing has been said about African descent since their
                ancestors were brought here against their will. Although the different nations that
                now make up Europe argued against this reform, the democracy claimed by the US once
                again won and there was
                nothing they could do but take back their people. More news will be given to the
                public once the bills have been signed and when the United States finds the
                resources to deport 300 million people. </p>
    </body>
    <footer>
      <share type="facebook"/>
      <share type="twitter"/>
      <share type="email"/>
      <share type="other"/>
      <related_links url=""/>
    </footer>
  </article>
  <!-- paste your genre here, after <DOC> and before the <docReview> section -->
</DOC>
