<?xml-model href="../schema_1111.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../testing_format.xsl"?><DOC>
  <article>
    <header>
      <article_title>Gary Johnson’s Media Meltdown Leads to All Time High Favorability of
                21%</article_title>
      <author>Author
            <!--deidentified element--></author>
      <category>News in Brief</category>
      <date>November 11, 2016</date>
      <identification type="volume">52</identification>
      <identification type="issue">68</identification>
      <tags>Politics, Politicians, Election, Gary Johnson, Hillary Clinton, Donald Trump</tags>
      <share type="facebook"/>
      <share type="twitter"/>
      <share type="email"/>
      <share type="other"/>
    </header>
    <body>
      <image url="http://media.breitbart.com/media/2016/05/wi/ap_gary-johnson_ap-photo-e1464287585747.jpg"/>
      <p><location>BOULDER, CO</location>Gary Johnson’s campaign has now been noticed by the
                general public after the traumatic, hard-to-watch video of him surfaced the
                Internet. The video showed a hot-tempered Johnson defending the inevitable
                “why are you even in the campaign?” question. The Libertarian Party candidate
                assures a win after re-watching his public media meltdown about the two main
                candidates. <quote>“Just look at the polls, Anderson. I’m at a whole 4.6% right now!
                    I’d say I got this one in the bag. Oh boy is it looking good for me, huh? We’re
                    practically on double digits! Just wait until the fourth debate and my numbers
                    will shoot way up.”</quote> said a red-faced Johnson, who added that his
                favorability numbers (of just 21%) are higher than “any president in the history of
                America”. After having a private conversation with Johnson’s VP pick- William Weld-
                we learned a great deal of useful information. <quote>“Really I don’t know what Gary
                    and I are still doing here. He’s a lost cause, in all seriousness.”</quote> Weld
                also added that Gary Johnson will be <quote>“the most irrelevant presidential
                    candidate in modern US history”</quote>. We visited Weld at the Libertarian
                Party office a week later only to find him emptying the office. I think we all know
                what this means.</p>
    </body>
    <footer>
      <share type="facebook"/>
      <share type="twitter"/>
      <share type="email"/>
      <share type="other"/>
      <related_links url="#"/>
      <ad/>
    </footer>
  </article>
  <!-- leave this section for peer review and assessment -->
</DOC>
