<?xml-model href="../schema_3302.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><!--the second line in the document associates the schema, so be sure not to change it-->
<DOC>
  <docHead>
    <!--required header includes metadata about the assignment (title, author, version)-->
    <title>Modeling and Producing Genre</title>
    <author>Name
            <!--deidentified element--></author>
    <version n="1" date="2016-08-01"/>
  </docHead>
  <cover_letter>
    <header>
      <name>
            Name de-identified<!--deidentified element--></name>
      <contact_info>
        <!-- One or More Contact -->
        <contact type="address">address<!--deidentified element--></contact>
        <contact type="address">address<!--deidentified element--></contact>
        <contact type="phone">phone<!--deidentified element--></contact>
        <contact type="email">email<!--deidentified element--></contact>
      </contact_info>
    </header>
    <greeting>Dear Hiring Committee: </greeting>
    <intro_para>
      <intent type="purpose">I am writing to apply for the MotorSports development engineer
                position at A123 Systems Inc. listed on Northeastern University’s job search
                website.</intent>
      <reason>I was excited to see a growing company invested in making progress into the
                future of clean energy in the automotive industry.</reason>
      <proposition>I have experience with startups similar to A123 and find that I am most driven in
                such an environment. </proposition>
    </intro_para>
    <para_background>
      <experience type="work">Working at Amphenol PCD, I was introduced to the types of
                standards mandated by military and aerospace industries. The rigorous standards
                implemented on us by ITAR and military arms suppliers taught me the importance of
                well-organized and effective documentation. This job is also where I became
                accomplished using <programs>Pro-E/Creo</programs> and implementing <skills>quality
                    control processes</skills>. </experience>
    </para_background>
    <para_background>
      <experience type="work">While working at Infinium, Inc., I worked on a small research
                team refining a process to create primary aluminum via electrolysis. I modelled in
                    <programs>AutoCAD Inventor</programs> and helped to <skills>build
                    infrastructure</skills> for the developing process. I also performed material
                compatibility tests and <skills>post experiment analysis using x-ray diffraction,
                    scanning electron microscopy, and data analysis</skills> in
                    <programs>MatLab.</programs></experience>
    </para_background>
    <para_background>
      <experience type="school">Aside from my work experience, I am a recent student at
                Northeastern University. In my labs and classes, I have developed strong technical
                writing and communication skills, the ability to work effectively with teams of
                people, and resourceful problem solving skills. </experience>
    </para_background>
    <para_closing>
      <compatability>I believe I work best in a fast paced, energetic environment and think I
                would be able to integrate well into a team like A123 Systems' MotorSports. </compatability>
      <next_step>I would welcome the opportunity to further discuss the position and my
                qualifications in the near future. </next_step>
      <acknowledgment>Thank you very much for your consideration! </acknowledgment>
    </para_closing>
    <signature>
      <salutation>Sincerely,</salutation>
      <pb/>
      <pb/>
      <pb/>
      <name>
            Name de-identified<!--deidentified element--></name>
    </signature>
  </cover_letter>
</DOC>
