<?xml-model href="../schema_1111.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../testing_format.xsl"?><DOC>
  <article>
    <header>
      <article_title>Incredible! Student manages to watch entire Game of Thrones series during
                Chemistry Lectures</article_title>
      <author>Author
            <!--deidentified element--></author>
      <category>Education</category>
      <date>November 8, 2016</date>
      <identification type="volume">1</identification>
      <identification type="issue">1</identification>
      <tags>Student | Chemistry | HBO | Game of Thrones | Lecture | College | Freshman</tags>
      <share type="facebook"/>
      <share type="twitter"/>
      <share type="email"/>
      <share type="other"/>
    </header>
    <body>
      <image url="https://www.michigandaily.com/sites/default/files/leg/imagecache/fullnode/tmn.NEW_.classrooms.1-256-11003.jpg"/>
      <p><location>BOSTON, MA--</location> At Northeastern University, we found a first-year
                student that managed to watch the entire series of the popular HBO Series 'Game of
                Thrones' entirely while he was attending his chemistry lectures. Jason Peters, the
                freshman engineer states, <quote>"You know everyone kept raving about how good Game
                    of Thrones was that I figured I would give it a whirl. I was hooked almost
                    instantly."</quote> This incredible feat of determination and perseverance was
                no easy task, as our experts calculated that he needed to be watching the show a
                whopping 93% of the hours he was in class. A classmate says, <quote>"I don't even
                    know why he shows up. I have actually never seen him looking up from his
                    computer. So much wasted tuition money."</quote> Once Peters was completely
                caught up in the show, he promptly shut his laptop and exited the classroom,
                completely oblivious to the professor at the front of the classroom. The professor
                paused for a moment, puzzled as he didn't recognize Peters whatsoever, but quickly
                returned to the lecture. As he was leaving, we asked Peters why he was so
                disinterested in chemistry, and couldn't watch the show during his free time, and he
                replied, <quote>"That was chemistry?"</quote></p>
    </body>
    <footer>
      <share type="facebook"/>
      <share type="twitter"/>
      <share type="email"/>
      <share type="other"/>
      <related_links url="http://fa16.kevingeraldsmith.com/project_page.php?transformed=true&amp;id=li.em&amp;proj=2">Great, The Uber Driver is Playing His F*cking Mixtape</related_links>
      <related_links url="http://fa16.kevingeraldsmith.com/project_page.php?transformed=true&amp;id=mi.as&amp;proj=2">Gary Johnson Claims Media Meltdown Helped His Campaign, VP Claims
                Otherwise</related_links>
    </footer>
  </article>
</DOC>
